<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DSGV1</string>
    <string name="lang_passwd">Password</string>
    <string name="lang_Vault_name">Vault name</string>
    <string name="Open_The_Vault">Open The Vault</string>
    <string name="Backup_Restore">Backup &amp; Restore</string>
    <string name="Create_a_new_Vault">Create a New Vault</string>
    <string name="Return">Return</string>
    <string name="Expert_Mode">Expert Mode</string>
    <string name="Version">Version</string>
    <string name="Select_your_language">Select your language:</string>
    <string name="Vault_Name_or_Password_cant_be_empty">Vault Name or Password can\'t be empty!</string>
    <string name="Wrong_credentials">Wrong credentials!</string>
    <string name="New_contact_has_been_saved">New contact has been saved!</string>
    <string name="Contact_name_cant_be_empty">Contact name can\'t be empty!</string>
    <string name="Cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="Please_open_your_vault">Please open your vault.</string>
    <string name="Decrypting_in_progress">Decrypting in progress...</string>
    <string name="You_have_a_Voice_message">You have a Voice message!</string>
    <string name="Do_you_want_me_to_play_it">Do you want me to play it?</string>
    <string name="Yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="No">No</string>
    <string name="Contact_Import">Contact Import</string>
    <string name="Name">Name</string>
    <string name="Save">Save</string>
    <string name="Expert_mode_has_been_enabled">Expert mode has been enabled.</string>
    <string name="Expert_mode_has_been_disabled">Expert mode has been disabled.</string>
    <string name="Export">Export</string>
    <string name="Restore">Restore</string>
    <string name="Delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="WARNING">WARNING</string>
    <string name="You_are_about_to_restore_a_backup">You are about to restore a backup...</string>
    <string name="Wipe_all_date">Current data will be permanently deleted. Do you really want to proceed?</string>
    <string name="Delete_backup">You are about to delete a backup file...</string>
    <string name="Are_You_Sure">Do you really want to proceed?</string>
    <string name="Data_Encryption">Data Encryption in progress...</string>
    <string name="Backup_has_been_created">Backup has been created!</string>
    <string name="MSG_Backup_Done">Please keep in mind that the just created backup has been saved locally, to export the backup click on it and choose for \'Export the backup\' to save it preferably on a USB stick. As backups contain only encrypted data, you can save your backups everywhere you want, but we don\'t recommend online cloud services to be used as a storage of any sensitive data... Just because RSA encryption is still unbreakable as today it doesn\'t mean it will be still unbreakable by tomorrow.</string>
    <string name="Ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="No_backup_yet">You haven\'t create any backup yet.</string>
    <string name="Create_a_Backup">Create a Backup</string>
    <string name="MSG_new_vault">* You can create as many vaults as you want. \n\n * Each vault will have a different public vault address. This helps you to separate works and private info or anonymous usage etc... \n\n * Each vault will be created and get saved on this device. No information whatsoever will ever be saved on any server or cloud services etc... \n\n * As every information on this device get encrypted and stored locally, you need to make a backup regularly when you create a new vault or add new information to your vault, password manager etc... \n\n * As backups contain only encrypted data, you can save your backups everywhere you want, but we don\'t recommend online cloud services to be used as a storage of any sensitive data... Just because RSA encryption is still unbreakable as today it doesn\'t mean it will be still unbreakable by tomorrow. \n\n * You can use the same vault name for different vaults as long as the passwords are different! Or use the same password as long as the vault names are different. The combination of your vault name and password grant access to the vault. \n\n * If you create a new vault using existing vault name and password combination DigiSafeGuard will just act like a new vault has been created. This is not a bug but a security measure! There will be no warning that a vault exists. \n\n * Vault names will also get encrypted. Even when a hacker gets physical access to this device he can\'t see any data as laterally every piece of information that you can think of will get encrypted before saving, like vault names, contact names, passwords etc... \n\n * Used encryption is based on RSA encryption in conjunction with AES for particular operations and doesn\'t rely on key storage of the Android operation system. This makes encryptions and decryptions slower and functions much more limited and less user-friendly, however, grant a much higher security level what makes this vault different than any other known app out there. RSA 4096 bit encryption is known as the most secure and unbreakable encryption method today. DigiSafeGuard has been designed with maximum security in mind and unfortunately, this can sometimes lead to less user-friendliness or slower operation. However, you can count on the most secure vault ever created. \n\n * DigiSafeGuard can be used in 2 different ways. Online and offline mode. \n\n Online mode:\n When you install and operate this app (DigiSafeGuard) on your regular smartphone having internet access, you still are exposed to the hackers as everyone having remote access to your phone screen can see the information that is visually available to you. Even though DigiSafeGuard has been designed to use cryptography most securely, it can\'t guarantee that a hacker doesn\'t watch your screen when you are typing your secrets information. \n\n Offline mode:\n You can also install this app on any other android device that doesn\'t have an internet connection, for example, an old smartphone that you don\'t use anymore. This makes DigiSafeGuard as secure as it ever can be as you can be 100% sure that no intruder will ever get remote access to your vault information. When using DigisafeGuard in offline mode you can use the QRcode data transfer method to send and receive messages and other data.</string>
    <string name="Creating_new_encryption_keys">Creating new encryption keys...</string>
    <string name="New_Vault_Creation">New Vault Creation</string>
    <string name="Your_new_vault_has_been_created">Your new vault has been created!</string>
    <string name="Vault_Public_Address">Vault Public Address</string>
    <string name="Close_The_Vault">Close The Vault</string>
    <string name="Crypto_Wallet">Crypto Wallet</string>
    <string name="Archive_Manager">Archive Manager</string>
    <string name="Passwords_Manager">Passwords Manager</string>
    <string name="Read_a_Message">Read a Message</string>
    <string name="Send_a_Message">Send a Message</string>
    <string name="Contact_Manager">Contact Manager</string>
    <string name="Not_a_valid_message">Not a valid message!</string>
    <string name="SCU_DSG_under_construction">Both DigiSafeGuard and Securypto Blockchain is still under heavy development. This feature is unfortunately not ready yet.</string>
    <string name="Manual_Input">Manual Input</string>
    <string name="Read_from_Clipboard">Read from Clipboard</string>
    <string name="Read_by_QR_Code">Read by QR Code</string>
    <string name="Info">Info</string>
    <string name="lang_not_ready">This language has not been ready yet. If you want to help translating, please contact us on our telegram channel or send an email to dev@securypto.io</string>
    <string name="Show_Record">Show Record</string>
    <string name="Credentials">Credentials</string>
    <string name="Description">Description</string>
    <string name="Username">Username</string>
    <string name="data_wipe_confim">Data will be erased. Are you Sure?</string>
    <string name="Add_New_Credentials">Add New Credentials</string>
    <string name="data_saved">Data has been saved!</string>
    <string name="no_passwd_manager_data">Your Password Manager is empty.</string>
    <string name="Restarting_QR_Dance">Restarting QR Dance...</string>
    <string name="Anonymous_Transfer">Anonymous Transfer</string>
    <string name="MSG_SCU_send">You can in the future send your messages using Securypto Blockchain Anonymously. However Securypto Blockchain is still under heavy development and not ready yet. For the time being you can use other unsecure channels like whatsapp, gmai, telegram etc... You\'r messages will still be encrypted and secure but will be traceable unlike using Securypto Blockchain.</string>
    <string name="Your_archive_is_empty">Your archive is empty.</string>
    <string name="Search">Search...</string>
    <string name="Select_an_Archive">Select an Archive</string>
    <string name="Text_and_Notes">Text and Notes</string>
    <string name="Audio_Files">Audio Files</string>
    <string name="Pictures">Pictures</string>
    <string name="Save_as">Save as...</string>
    <string name="Name_cant_be_empty">Name can\'t be empty!</string>
    <string name="Coudnt_take_a_picture">Coudn\'t take a picture!</string>
    <string name="Recording">Recording...</string>
    <string name="Stop_Recording">Stop Recording</string>
    <string name="MSG_contact">This vault doesn\'t have any contact yet.\n\n * To send a message you need the vault address of the receiver. \n\n Easy Mode:\n 1. Ask your contact for his public vault address.\n 2. Click on his message and share it with DigiSafeGuard, DSG will automatically recognize the vault address and imported for you.\n\n Expert Mode:\n 1. Ask your contact for his public vault address.\n 2. Click on import contact.\n 3. Import his vault address by scanning his vault address QR code or import manually using the clipboard if you got his address as a plain text.\n \n\n * You can switch between Easy and Expert mode as often as you like. There is no compromise in security levels whatsoever. Using Expert mode will just give you more options to choose from. Operation mode can be changed under the Settings page. \n\n * You need to do this only once for every contact. \n\n * As contact name you can choose whatever you want. All contact names will be encrypted too and are not visible if a hacker gets physical access to your device.</string>
    <string name="Picture">Picture</string>
    <string name="Show_contact_address">Show contact address</string>
    <string name="File">File</string>
    <string name="Voice_Message">Voice_Message</string>
    <string name="Text_Message">Text Message</string>
    <string name="Encrypte_the_message">Encrypte the message</string>
    <string name="Decrypte_the_message">Decrypte the message</string>
    <string name="Encrypte_and_Save_in_Archive">Encrypte and Save in Archive</string>
    <string name="Subject_Must_be_unique">Subject... (Must be unique)</string>
    <string name="Subject_cant_be_empty">Subject can\'t be empty!</string>
    <string name="Description...">Description...</string>
    <string name="Password...">Password...</string>
    <string name="Username...">Username...</string>
    <string name="Vault_Name...">Vault Name...</string>
    <string name="Vault_Password...">Vault Password...</string>
    <string name="Scanning...">Scanning...</string>
    <string name="Exist">Exist! Do you want to override this record?</string>
    <string name="Screenshot">Screenshot</string>
    <string name="Screenshot_confim">Enabling Screenshot feature, will allow other apps to see your screen! We highly discouraged enabling this option unless you are using DigiSafeGuard in the offline mode.</string>
    <string name="Permission_notes">DigiSafeGuard app will ask your permission only for the basic functions that are needed to operate, no data what so ever will be send to any cloud services or servers using a hidden background process without your knowledge like other similar apps and if you are using DSG in offline-mode, you don\'t even need to trust DSG development team!\n\n* Camera: Needed to send encrypted photos or saving encrypted pictures in your vault archive.\n\n* Audio: Needed for to send encrypted audio messages or saving encrypted audio notes in your vault archive.\n\n* Storage: Needed for example to import or save encrypted backups, share messages to other apps etc… Every piece of information will get encrypted prior saving.\n\n* Network: Needed to share the encrypted messages using Securypto Blockchain. if you are using DSG in offline-mode, which we highly recommend, this wouldn\'t be an security or privacy issue in anyway. </string>
    <string name="Permission_header">We take security and privacy highly serious!</string>
    <string name="Create_a_scu_wallet">Create a new wallet</string>
    <string name="Your_wallet_is_empty">You haven\'t create any wallet yet.</string>
    <string name="BTC_TEXT">BTC</string>
    <string name="SCU_TEXT">SCU</string>
    <string name="ETH_TEXT">ETH</string>
    <string name="Wallet_creation_in_progress">New wallet creation in progress...</string>
    <string name="Show_QR_XPRIV">Show XPRIV Key</string>
    <string name="Show_QR_XPUB">Show XPUB Key</string>
    <string name="Show_Balance">Show Balance</string>
    <string name="Cant_delete_need_expert_mode">You can\'t delete a sub-wallet by default as a security measure. Doing so, you will lost access to the funds associated with this sub-wallet. If you still want to do this and know what you are doing, turn on the expert mode in the settings.</string>
    <string name="Cant_overwrite_need_expert_mode">Your chosen sub-wallet name exist already and cannot be overwritten. Access has been disabled by default. If you still want to do this and know what you are doing, turn on the expert mode in the settings and delete it first.</string>
    <string name="Save_wallet_as">Choose a name for this new sub-wallet.</string>
    <string name="xpub_text">This is your Public Key. We strongly advise against showing your xPub to untrusted third parties. Someone having access to your XPub can\'t spend your funds but it will grant him access to your payments history and it\'s a serious privacy issue.</string>
    <string name="xpriv_text">This is your Private Key. We strongly advise against showing your XPriv to anyone! Knowledge of the XPriv will enable someone to access your funds!</string>
    <string name="xpriv_text_need_expert">This is your Private Key. We strongly advise against showing your XPriv to anyone! Knowledge of the XPriv will enable someone to access your funds! Access has been disabled by default. If you really want to do this and know what you are doing, enable the expert mode in the settings first.</string>
    <string name="xpub_text_offline_mode">This is your Public Key. Scan this QR using DigiSafeGuard installed on your second smartphone that have internet connection enabled to access your balance. We strongly advise against showing your xPub to untrusted third parties. Someone having access to your XPub can\'t spend your funds but it will grant him access to your payments history and it\'s a serious privacy issue.</string>


</resources>
